- Now here's an American
combo of the Young Rascals
so let's bring them on.
(applause)
♪ Good lovin' ♪
♪ - I was feelin' so bad ♪
♪ I asked my family
doctor just what I had ♪
♪ I said, Doctor ♪
♪ Doctor ♪
♪ Mr. M.D. ♪
♪ Now can you tell me ♪
♪ What's ailin' me? ♪
♪ Doctor ♪
♪ He said, "Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah" ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yes, indeed,
all I really need ♪
♪ Is good lovin' ♪
♪ Gimme that good lovin' ♪
♪ Good lovin' ♪
♪ All I need is lovin' ♪
♪ Good lovin', baby ♪
♪ Honey please,
squeeze me tight ♪
♪ Squeeze me tight ♪
♪ Now don't you want
your baby to be alright? ♪
♪ Be alright ♪
♪ I said baby ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Now it's for sure ♪
♪ It's for sure ♪
♪ I got the fever ♪
♪ You got the cure ♪
♪ Got the cure ♪
♪ C'mon baby, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Could it be all
I really need? ♪
♪ Give me that
good good lovin ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ All I need is lovin' ♪
♪ Come on love me baby ♪
(Guitar strumming)
(drums pound)
(organ playing)
♪ Good lovin' ♪
♪ All I want is love ♪
♪ All I need is love ♪
♪ Love is all in the mornin' ♪
♪ Love is late at night ♪
♪ Ohh, love, love love ♪
(guitar strumming)
(applause)